prongo.com 2019-02-16

# Privacy Policy - Prongo.com

Privacy Policy  
We at Prongo.com want you and your children to feel safe whenever visiting and using our site. Prongo.com believes that interactive fun is a way to educational success. Children using the Internet should have a positive, safe, and rewarding experience. We at prongo.com stride in earning your trust and take pride in your confidence, you have entrusted us with your most precious gift, your children. We feel it is our responsibility to build an educational site where children can feel safe and have fun.

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.

Your family’s privacy is important to us. Prongo.com only collects personal information in the ecard features and cool links but does not store this information. Prongo.com is prohibited from conditioning a child’s participation in an activity on the child’s disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity. We encourage children to use nicknames or unidentifiable names when making site submissions to Prongo.com. We would like to inform parents and teachers to encourage children not to use their Internet access screen names when submitting forms to Prongo.com or any other children’s sites.

We recommend here at Prongo.com that you discuss safety on the Internet with your child/children. Children should never give out any personal information without getting permission from a parent or legal guardian.

Prongo.com provides links to other sites that are children oriented. We do visit these sites regularly but cannot be responsible for the content on these sites. Please contact us if you feel a site, and/or a link, is not suitable or is inappropriate for children. We will look into the situation regarding any concerns you may have and handle it promptly.

We at Prongo.com want you to interact with your children on prongo.com. Our goal is to bring families together to learn and grow minds. We want it to be safe, fun, and most of all educationally enriching.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org
